Accio which programming language should
I start with now this question is very
hard to answer correctly the reason why
is because when you ask me that question
I don't know you I don't know what you
want I don't know what you want to build
so if I tell you oh just learn Python
HTML CSS I will be robbing of an
explanation that you deserve in a
background that you need to understand
I'm going to answer you with giving you
five programming languages the more
popular ones why are they used if you
learn them where are you gonna get where
are you gonna go the person we start
with is C and C++ C is a programming
language designed for a very very low
level performance very very very very
close to the machine so for example you
can use C to program air currents or
smart TVs or smart fridges stuff like
that something that has a little bit of
yes programming but it doesn't have lots
of memory also if you learned C and C++
most likely you're also gonna find a job
in those big companies or enterprises
that have a make software's that require
performance for example you're gonna end
up work in a project like Photoshop or
Premiere Pro like in a company like
Adobe that you have to make software
that really needs performance next
programming language Java Java is very
popular in Korea in most of the time
Java three popular in corporations
government banks and all that stone
nowadays is used to build Enterprise web
applications if you learn Java you're a
hundred percent gonna get a job there
are many many jobs for Java they are not
most of the time in very fast-moving
startups Java is usually used by
enterprise as ad set or when you need to
integrate with older legacy systems some
some banks are in Java most governments
are in Java company that integrates with
these kind of services then you're gonna
need Java also if you learn Java you are
going to be able to program Android
applications so if you want to be like
an enterprise developer to do you know
that you have a job and to have a
safe job in an environment that doesn't
move as fast as for example front-end
development then Java is for you also if
you want to be Android developer 100%
and you love Android then Java is the
place for you next one Python I think
the easiest choice for a beginner and
the reason why I say this is because
python is very very very very
multi-purpose
for example in Python you can find how
to hack computers which is how I learned
also with Python you can do machine
learning also with Python you can do
data signs also in Python you can do
data visualization also with Python you
can do scraping the internet also you
can build websites there's many as you
can see you can do many many many things
beginner friendly language is not as
ugly as Java and it's not as ugly as C
you need to remember that that the
closer the language is to the system the
lower level the more ugly it is python
is a very free language to read and
that's why beginners liked it so much
because it doesn't scare you at the
beginning like see if you see see oh my
god what up okay javascript but let's
make one programming language let's call
it HTML CSS in JavaScript if you want to
build websites and that is the main
focus of what you want to learn to
program then go for HTML CSS in
JavaScript that is how you start making
website some people will tell you oh if
you want to make a website then go for
Python because Python makes websites as
well yes you can make a website with
Python the difference is that with HTML
CSS and JavaScript you learn by building
something that is visually attractive
for you and also you learn how the web
works from the ground up from the from
nothing to everything so when you want
to become a web developer and if that's
what you want to do then HTML CSS in
JavaScript now also if you learn
JavaScript and you like it a lot you're
going to be able to build barry to build
many dynamic websites you can also make
some iOS android applications you can
also program the backend now javascript
is also kind of multi-purpose like
python is but javascript is very old and
PHP is to build backends you can build
backends with PHP and PHP runs
everywhere most of the internet runs on
PHP why because it is this thing called
WordPress WordPress runs with PHP and
many websites use WordPress for many
many many things also PHP is stable the
community is big I don't usually use it
that much I learnt it before but for me
is not it's not my thing I prefer Python
or node.js but also if you learn PHP and
you want to be able to do stuff for
WordPress if you want to be able to do
stuff for things like Magento or Drupal
stuff like that like content management
systems then PHP is your guy oh alright
my people that's it so now is your turn
ask yourself the question what do you
want to build and then choose right
start with why first know yourself and
then all the answers will be in front of
you thank you for watching let me know
what you think about this video I know
many people are going to disagree
many people are gonna agree please
comment and ask me more questions I'm
very very happy that I'm getting more
and more more questions every day no
question is stupid all questions are
loved thank you again for watching don't
forget to be happy eat kimchi and sang
gibson bike